제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
1977년 2월 13일
February 13th, 1977
일요일 오후
Sunday Afternoon
에릭네 지하실
Eric Forman's Basement
저리 비켜, 이 곰탱아
Get off me, you moose.
에릭, 너 거기 있는 줄도 몰랐어
너 운동해서 몸 좀 불려야 겠다
Eric, I didn't see you sitting there.
You should really work on bulking up.
운동은 네가 해야 될껄?
Maybe you should
really work on bulking up.
뭘 보는 거야?
What are you watching?
"길리건 표류기" 한다
Gilligan is on.
너네 바닥에서 뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing in the floor?
맞아, 너희는 방도 없냐?
Yeah. Why don't
you guys get a room?
우리도 방 있어, 하이드
We have a room, Hyde.
여기가 바로 내방이야
It's called my basement.
나 집에 갈래
I'm going home.
잘 있어, 얘들아
Bye, guys.
도나, 내일 저녁 도서관에서
만나기로 한 거 잊지마
Donna, don't forget. I'll see you
tomorrow night at the library.
알았어
Yeah, right.
내가 집에 데려다 줄께
I'll walk you home.
- 바로 옆집 살잖아
- 알아
- She lives right next door.
- Yeah.
도나
Donna,
내일 저녁 말인데..
about tomorrow night.
너랑 둘이 저녁 먹으러
갈려고 했었어
I was thinking that maybe
you and I could go out to dinner.
발렌타인 데이잖아?
For Valentine's Day?
하이드가 도서관에서
공부하자고 했는데
Hyde asked me to study
at the library.
그건 아무때나
할 수 있잖아, 그렇지?
I mean, you can do
that anytime, right?
그래, 저녁먹으러 가자
Yeah, I'd love to go.
잘 됐다
That's great.
우리 데이트하는 거야
So then it's a date.
우리 첫 데이트네
Our first.
맞아, 우리가 키스한 건
데이트로 안 친다면
Yeah, if you don't count
all the times I mauled you.
그래
Yeah.
안 쳤어. 그러니까..
Which I don't. So....
안녕, 얘들아
Hey, guys.
무슨 일들이야?
So, what's going on?
나중에 다시 얘기하자
I'll talk to you guys later.
에릭
So, Eric...
도나랑 무슨 얘기를 그렇게
뜨겁게 한 거야?
what were you and Donna
talking all hot and heavy about?
- 네 머리 얘기
- 정말?
- Your hair.
- Really?
아니
No.
내일 발렌타인데이 기념으로
저녁 먹으면서 데이트할거야
We're going out to dinner
tomorrow night. For Valentine's Day.
아냐, 아냐, 아냐
No, no, no.
도나는 나랑 내일 저녁에
도서관에서 공부하기로 했어
Donna and I are going to the library
to study tomorrow night.
발렌타인 데이에?
누가 발렌타인 데이에 공부를 해?
On Valentine's Day?
Who studies on Valentine's Day?
데이트 약속 잡을 때는
발렌타인 데이인줄 몰랐어
I didn't know it was Valentine's Day
when I made the date.
공부 약속
To study.
약속을 잊어 버렸나봐
I'm sure she just forgot about you.
금방 얘기했는데 무슨 소리야?
We just talked about it
a minute ago.
여자들이 원래 그렇잖아
Women. You know, I mean....
어쨌든 도나한테
내 졸업반지를 줄거야
Anyway, I'm gonna give Donna
my class ring.
반지는 무슨 반지야
No, forget rings.
도나한테 점수따고 싶으면 내가
끝내주는 펑크뮤직 테잎을 빌려줄께
You wanna score with Donna,
use my super funk eight-track.
어쨌든 이제 정식으로
사귈 때가 된 거 같아
Anyway, I figure it's time
to make it official.
도나는 어떤 바보가 자기를
덮쳐주기를 기다리고 있거든
She's just been waiting for any jerk
to swoop down on her.
네가 그 바보라 이거군
And you're that jerk.
어떤 다른 바보보다는
내가 낫지
Better me than some other jerk.
왜 날 쳐다봐?
그 다른 바보는 하이드잖아
Why are you looking at me?
Hyde is the other jerk.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x16 The First Date
Feb 14, 1999 on FOX
에릭이 도나랑 데이트하러
가 버리면 우린 차가 없잖아
So, if Eric and Donna
are going out Saturday night...
that means we have no wheels.
우리 아빠 차를 빌릴 수 있을 거야
I can borrow my dad's car.
가죽시트 깔린 '링컨'이야
It's a Lincoln. Leather.
우리 이렇게 하자
You know what we should do?
하이드랑 페즈는 버리고
뒷좌석에서 데이트하는 거야
We should ditch Hyde and Fez
and make out in the backseat.
너무 크게 말한 거 아냐?
You said that out loud.
그래도 상관없어
Yeah, I don't care.
아! 알았다
우리 나막신 사러 가자
Yeah, I know.
We can go shopping for clogs.
7시에 나 데리러 와
Pick me up at 7:00.
재밌게 놀아라. 난 빠질래
Have fun, man. I'm out.
우리 쇼핑하러 안 갈거야
We won't be shopping.
우리 또 그거 할 거야
We'll be doing it. Again.
그게 바로 우리가 할 일이니까
우린 그거 한다!
'Cause that's what we do.
We do it!
그럼 나도 낄래
Then I'm in.
니가 낄 자리가 아냐, 페즈
No, you're not invited, Fez.
그럼 난 빠질래
Then I'm out.
그럼 나중에 보자
Yeah. Well, later.
너랑 나만 남은 것 같구나
가엾은 친구야
It looks like
it's just you and me, little buddy.
그래, 페즈
근데 이건 정말 잘못된 거야
Yeah, Fez.
Which is really wrong, man...
포먼이 딴지 걸기 전만 해도
도나는 나랑 약속했었단 말야
'cause I had plans with Donna.
Until Forman snaked me.
도나가 냄새나는 도서관 대신 멋진
레스토랑에 가려고 할지 누가 알았겠냐?
Who would have thought she would
rather go to a nice restaurant...
than a smelly, old library?
잘 생각해보면 웃길껄?
You will laugh later.
어디 한번 봐요
So, let me see.
이리 와서 엄마한테 보여드려라
Go ahead, show your mother.
어머나, 너무 멋지다
너무 멋진 재킷이야
Oh, my gosh, that is snazzy.
That is a snazzy jacket.
내가 같이 가길 천만 다행이지
레져 재킷을 사려고 하더라니까
Damn good thing I went with him.
He wanted to buy a leisure suit.
왜요, 아빠. 레져 재킷도 멋져요
다들 입는다구요
Come on, Dad. Leisure suits are cool.
Everybody wears them.
레져 재킷은 머저리들이나
입는 옷이라니까. 내 말 들어
Leisure suits are for dumbasses.
Believe me.
안녕, 에릭
Hey, there, Eric.
데이트 때문에 쫙 빼입은 거냐?
Looking sharp for your big date?
쬐끄맣던 것들이 이제 커서
데이트를 하는 구나
Who knew our two little tykes
would grow up to be dating.
아, 좋은 생각이 있어요
Oh, no. I have an idea.
내일 저녁에 같이 식사해요
부모들 끼리요
Let's have dinner tomorrow night.
Just the parents.
내가 퐁듀를 만들게요
I'll fondue.
좋아요
Yeah.
그러면서 우리 아이들의 미래에
대해서도 얘기를 좀 해보죠
And that'll give us a chance
to talk about their future.
맞아요. 결혼식은 성대하게 하자구요
Right. We can plan a big wedding.
농담하시는 거 아는데
그만 좀 하심 안돼요? 제발요
I know you're joking.
But could you please stop? Please?
- 있잖니, 나는..
- 우리 차를 빌려줄께
- You know, I've....
- You can borrow our car.
여자들은 꽃장식을 좋아한단다
Girls love corsages.
'빈야드' 레스토랑은
양파 튀김이 맛있다, 알았지?
They got a fried onion brick
at The Vineyard, right?
너 정말 기가 막힌다, 마이클
I don't believe you, Michael.
뭐가?
What?
우리 아빠 앞에서 나한테
그렇게 찐하게 키스하면 어떡해?
You can't just maul me
in front of my father.
너희 아빠는 눈치 못챘을 거야
I bet he didn't even notice.
너한테 그만하라고 소리치셨잖아
He yelled at you to stop it.
난 너한테 말하는 건 줄 알았어
I thought he was talking to you.
마이클, 문제가 있어
Okay. Michael, we have a problem.
우리 그 뒤로는..
Ever since we....
그거 한 뒤로?
Did it?
말 좀 예쁘게 할 수 없니?
Can you please use
a more beautiful term?
어떻게?
Like what?
'우리 사랑을 증명했다' 라던가
Like, proved our love.
그래. 그치만 "그거 했다"가
더 쿨하게 들려
Yeah. But "did it" sounds
so much cooler.
됐다, 백화점에나 데려다 줘
Okay, just take me to the mall.
진짜 쇼핑하러 갈 거 아니지, 안 그래?
We're not really going
shopping, are we?
아니긴, 나막신 살 거야
Yes, I need clogs.
Oh.
이런! 정말 멋진 재킷이구나
God darn!
That is a snazzy jacket.
갈색이 끝내주게 받는구나
Yes, sir. Brown is your color.
고마워요, 아빠
하지 말아요, 엄마
Thanks, Dad. No, Mom.
몇가지 당부해 두는데
꼭 풀코스로 시켜라
Let me tell you something,
order the dinner.
몇개만 골라서 시키는 짓은
촌놈들이나 하는 짓이야
A la carte's a sucker's bet.
And remember...
도나 의자 빼주는 거 잊지 말고
pull the chair out for her.
샐러드는 작은 포크로 먹는 거다
The small fork is for the salad.
이 재킷은 너 대학 졸업 때까지
입어야 되니까 뭐 흘리지 않게 조심해
And this jacket's gotta last you
all the way through college...
so don't spill any crap on it.
이거 받아라
Here you go. Have fun.
재밌게 놀고
Yeah.
- 갈까?
- 좋은 생각이야
- Shall we?
- Good God, yes.
웃어
Smile.
미지도 찍는데 나도 찍을래
Now, if she gets to do it,
I get to do it.
여보, 애들 출발하잖아
Kitty, he's leaving.
부담감 장난 아니네
Talk about pressure.
그래, 아주 큰 일인가 봐
Yeah, I mean, this is a huge deal.
우리 부모님들한테는
To our parents.
"Disco Lady"
by Johnnie Taylor
그래서 인제 뭐 할 거야?
So what do you wanna do?
나도 몰라
넌 뭐하고 싶은데?
I don't know, man.
What do you want to do?
'허브'에나 가자
빵빵한 여자애 하나 봐뒀어
Let's go to The Hub.
I've got my eye on this plump girl.
좋은 얘기다만 난 됐어
Sounds good, man, but I'll pass.
불쌍한 하이드
Poor Hyde.
뭐가?
What?
친구의 애인 도나를 사랑하잖아
You love Donna,
and she's with your good friend Eric.
그래서?
And?
세상에서 제일 오래된 얘깃거리지
And that's the oldest story
in the world.
게다가 슬프고
And a sad one at that.
나한테도 찬스가 있었는데
내가 그만 둔거야, 알아?
You know what, man?
I had a chance, and I didn't take it.
일단 포먼이 도나한테 반지를 주면
정식으로 사귀게 되는 거야
And once Forman gives her that ring,
man, they're going out.
그렇게 되면 도나를 꼬시는 건
정말 치사한 짓이 되는 거지
And it would be really scummy
to hit on her then.
그렇다고 안 하겠다는 건 아니고
그냥 치사한 짓이라는 거야
Not that I wouldn't do it.
It'd just be really scummy.
도나한테 네 감정을 말 안하면
나중에 후회하게 될 걸?
If you don't tell Donna how you feel,
then you will regret it.
- '빈야드'에 가야겠다
- 잘 생각했어
- I'm going to The Vineyard.
- Good for you.
에릭한테 내가 그랬다고 말하지 마
지하실에서 쫓겨나기 싫거든
Just don't tell Eric what I said
because I really like his basement.
가격이 장난 아닌데
This is quite a menu.
그러게
Yeah.
돈은 충분히 있는 거지?
You got enough money?
그래, 내 꺼는
Yeah, for me.
미안. 너도 뭐 먹을려고 했었어?
I'm sorry. Were you gonna
eat something, too?
난 닭요리가 먹고 싶어
Actually, I'm in the mood for chicken.
이런 우연이 있나!
What a coincidence.
나도 제일 싼 거
주문할 생각이었거든
I, too, am ordering
the cheapest thing on the menu.
너 오늘 되게 근사하다
You look really nice tonight.
너도 그래
So do you.
있잖아, 도나..
Look, Donna--
안녕하세요!
Hello!
Can I start you folks off with drinks?
음료 먼저 주문하시겠습니까?
아, 네..
Sure--
난 맥주 주시오
I'll have a beer.
알겠습니다
All right.
저는 저 사람 먹는 아이스 티요
I'd like an iced tea.
- 몇살이냐고도 안 물어보는데
- 자켓 때문일거야
- He didn't even proof me.
- It must be the jacket.
- 아니면 구레나룻 때문이거나
- 웬 구레나룻?
- Or my sideburns.
- What sideburns?
여기 있잖아
These sideburns, right.
이걸 왜 퐁(fon)듀라고 하는지
모르겠어요
You know, I don't know
why they call it fondue.
펀(fun)듀라고 안하고요
정말 재밌는데요(fun)
They should call it fundue.
'Cause it is fun.
저는 퐁듀가 좋아요
미식가처럼 보이잖아요
I love fondue.
It's gourmet.
- 이제 어떻게 먹는 건데?
- 네, 우선요..
- So, what do we do here, Kitty?
- Okay, now. What you do is...
퐁듀 포크로
스테이크 한 조각을 찍어서
you put a piece of steak
on your fondue fork.
- 대체 이건 얼마나 뜨거워..
- 안돼요, 밥. 뽕듀되는 수 있어요
- Now, how hot exactly is the--
- No, Bob. That's a fondon't.
뜨거운 기름에 손을 넣으면 안되죠
Don't put your hand in the hot oil.
자네가 뜨거운 기름에 손 담그는
재주있는 줄은 미쳐 몰랐는데?
Who knew you couldn't
put your hand in the hot oil?
여기요, 닭이다, 닭, 닭, 닭
Here, chicken, chicken.
도나, 하지 마
Donna, please.
미안
Sorry.
- 너 괜찮아?
- 아주 좋아
- Are you okay?
- I am great.
너 취한 거 같은데
I think you're drunk.
내 생각에도 그래
I think I am, too.
술도 안 마셨는데 어떻게 취해?
How could I be drunk?
롱아일랜드 아이스 티에는
술이 다섯 잔 정도 들어있습니다
럼과 보드카 칵테일, 색깔만 아이스 티
There's about five shots of alcohol
in a Long Island Iced Tea.
- 롱아일랜드 아이스 티요?
- 네, 시키셨잖습니까?
- Long Island Iced Tea?
- Yeah, you guys ordered drinks.
- 나 한잔 더 할래요
- 아뇨, 괜찮아요
- I'm ready for another one.
- Nope, she's good.
고마워요
Thanks. Thank you.
난 네 쬐끄만 엉덩이가 좋아
I love your little butt, Eric.
너무 앙증맞아
It's so little.
Okay.
그리고 넌 너무 착해, 에릭
더럽게 착해
And you're so good, Eric.
You're so darn good.
- 커피 마셔야 겠다
- 넌 너무 착해서, 날 흥분시켜
- I think it's coffee time.
- You're so good, it makes me hot.
아니면 아이스 티 한잔 더 하거나
Or time for another Iced Tea maybe.
노래 해줘, 에릭
Sing to me, Eric.
안돼, 말도 안..
No, I don't think--
- 노래 해줘
- 난 못한다니까
- Sing me a song.
- I don't really--
안하면 소리지른다!
Do it or I'll scream!
♪ 다가왔다 멀어지고 ♪
♪ Move it in, move it out ♪
♪ 당겼다 풀어주고 ♪
♪ Shove it in, shove it out ♪
♪ 디스코 레이디 ♪
♪ Disco lady ♪
♪ 다가왔다 멀어지고 ♪
♪ Move it in, move it out ♪
♪ 밀고들어와.. 다같이 ♪
♪ Shove it in, all about ♪
야, 재키. 벌써 9시야
Well, Jackie. It's now 9:00.
오쉬코쉬의 모든 신발가게가
문닫을 시간이 된 거지
Which means
that every shoe store...
in the greater Oshkosh area
is closed for the night.
그럼, 인제 뭐하고 싶니?
So, what do you want to do now?
새로 나온 코르벳 보러 가자
Let's go look at the new Corvettes.
좋아
Yeah.
그러니까..
I mean....
아냐, 따분할 거 같아
No, that just sounds boring.
그럼 뭐하고 싶은데?
What do you wanna do?
나도 몰라
No, I don't know.
우리 이렇게 하면 어떨까?
Wait. You know what we could do?
우리 말이지..
We could....
다시 서로에게
사랑을 증명하는 거야
Prove our love to each other again.
아냐, 마이클
우린..
No, Michael.
We are not going to....
기회가 생길 때마다
사랑을 증명하지는 않을 거야
Prove our love,
every single time we have a chance.
왜 안돼?
Why not?
그렇게 하는 게 아니니까 그렇지
게다가 한번 했다고 해서
Because it doesn't work like that.
And just because we did it once...
그걸 계속 다시 해야 되는
것도 아니거든
does not mean
we're ever gonna do it again.
그게 무슨 미친 소리야!
Okay, now you're just talking crazy!
아냐, 마이클
No, Michael. No, I am not.
맨날 하게 될 거라고
생각했다면 네 착각이야
If you think that's how it's gonna work,
then you're wrong.
젠장, 재키
Damn, Jackie.
나는 저녁내 짜증나도
니 신발 보러 다녀줬더니
So I spent all night
looking for your stupid shoes...
앞으로는 안 할.. / 안해!
and we're not even gonna--/ No.
알았어
Fine.
너 정말 안해도 괜찮아?
Are you sure you're okay with that?
그래
Yeah.
좋아, 하자
Okay, let's do it.
- 젠장!
- 아얏!
- Crap.
- Ouch!
- 빌어먹을!
- 아 뜨!
- Damn!
- rmOw!
이런!
Geez!
내 눈깔!
My eye!
이런, 여긴 너무 번잡하다
God. It's so crowded in here.
에릭, 테이블 밑에서 만나자
Eric, meet me under the table.
도나, 안돼. 그러지 마
Donna, no. Look, no.
도나, 왜 이래
Look, Donna, come on.
웨이터?
Waiter?
난 가서 커피를 좀 가져올테니까
Okay. I'm gonna go get
you some coffee.
테이블 밑에 들어가지 말고
노래도 부르지 마
So, no going under the table,
and no singing.
금방 올께
I'll be right back.
이봐, 여기 닭요리 너무 잘해
People, the chicken here
is excellent.
하이드 왔어
Hyde's here.
안녕, 하이드
Hi, Hyde.
안녕, 도나
Hey, Donna.
포먼은 어디 갔어?
Where's Forman?
커피 가지러
Coffee.
할 얘기가 있는데 말야
Okay, look.
I'm just going to say this, all right?
도나, 난 너한테
특별한 감정이 있어
Donna, I have feelings for you.
너도 나한테 특별한 감정이
있다고 생각해
And I think that you
have feelings for me.
포먼이 너한테 반지를 줄 텐데
And Forman's gonna
give you his ring.
네가 그걸 받기 전에
다시 한번 생각해 줬으면..
And I hope that before you take it,
you think about--
삐이!
Beep!
안녕, 에릭? 하이드 왔어
Eric. Hyde's here.
하이디, 하이디, 하이디, 하이디
Heidi, Heidi, Heidi, Heidi.
남 데이트하는데 왠일이야
We're on a date here.
너만 아니었으면 우린 도서관에
같이 있었을 거야
Yeah, man. You shouldn't be...
because we were
supposed to be at the library.
하이드, 도나가 도서관에
가고 싶었으면 갔겠지
Hyde, if she wanted to be
at the library, she'd be at the library.
어머나
Oh, my God.
잠깐, "어머나"라니 무슨 뜻이야?
Wait. What do you mean
by "Oh, my God"?
- 어머나
- Oh, my God.
야, 내 애인이
다 토하고 왔을 때
Look, when my date's done puking...
넌 여기 없는 게 좋을 거야
you better not be here.
여기요?
Excuse me. Hi.
이거 포장 좀 해주시겠어요?
Could I get this
in a doggie bag, please?
고마워요
Thanks.
좀 서둘러 주세요
And I'm in a hurry.
Now....
너랑 아주 가까워진
느낌이야, 마이클
I feel so close to you, Michael.
마이클과 재키
재키와 마이클
Michael and Jackie.
Jackie and Michael.
근사하게 들리지 않니?
Doesn't that sound good?
마이클과 재키
Michael and Jackie.
진정한 사랑
True love,
변치 않고
always,
영원히
forever.
- 영원히?
- 영원히
- Forever?
- Forever.
댄스
Dances,
산책
long walks...
촛불
candles,
꽃
flowers.
애기들, 집
Babies, house.
족쇄, 사슬
Shackle, chain...
절망, 감옥, 죽음
despair, prison, death.
"갈매기 조나단은 깨닫게 됐어요"
Jonathan Livingston Seagull (갈매기의 꿈)
"Jonathan Seagull discovered...
"권태감과 공포와 분노 때문에"
"that boredom, fear, and anger...
"갈매기들의 수명이
짧을 수 밖에 없다는 것을요"
"are the reasons
a gull's life is so short.
"자신의 마음에서 그 생각들을 없애자"
"And with this gone from his thought...
"아주 오래 잘 살았습니다"
"he lived a long, fine life indeed."
브라보!
Bravo!
섹시한 토마토 같지 않아요?
Isn't she a hot tomato?
사랑을 하러 가자구
To the lovemaking.
오늘 너무 즐거웠어요
We had a wonderful time.
세상에!
My God!
됐어요, 갔어요
Okay, they're gone.
전엔 미치지 않았었잖아
They used to be normal.
대체 무슨 일이 있었던 거야?
What the hell happened to them
몰라요
I don't know.
미지는 고기 안 먹고 어떻게 산데요?
건강에 안 좋을텐데
소설 속 갈매기 조나단이 먹이사냥을 안함
How can she not eat meat?
That can't be healthy.
우리가 휴가 같이 가곤
했던 거 기억나?
Remember when
we used to go on vacation together?
밥하고 난 낚시가서
맥주를 마시곤 했지
Bob and I used to go fishing
and drink beers.
그땐 같이 즐겁게
지냈었는데 말이에요
I mean, we used to
have fun with them.
저 사람들 완전히 맛이 가 버렸군
Now they're into every fad there is.
모든건 변하기 마련이지
Things change, Kitty.
우린 안 변해요
We don't.
우린 변할 필요가 없지
We don't have to.
전통을 고수하잖아
We're classic.
있잖아..
You know...
오늘밤 미지가 노브라 더라구
Midge wasn't wearing a bra tonight.
네, 밥은 노팬티였구요
Yeah.
Bob wasn't wearing underwear.
아까 토할 때 내 머리카락
잡아줘서 고마워
Thanks for holding my hair
when I was....
내 신발에 안 토해 줘서 고마워
Just thanks for missing my shoes.
오늘 데이트 망쳐서 미안해
I guess I blew our big night.
아냐
No.
아냐, 괜찮아
내가 망칠 뻔 했었는데
Look, it's cool.
I thought I was gonna blow it...
네가 완전히 망쳐버렸잖아
나로선 잘된 거지
and then, I mean, you totally blew it.
So that's great.
내가 망쳤다고 말하는 바람에
네가 망쳐 버린 거야
You know, by telling me I blew it,
you basically just blew it. So....
그래도 나 너무 착하잖아
재킷도 주고 커피에다
And I was doing so good here
with the jacket and the coffee...
네 머리카락도 잡아주고
and holding your hair back.
네 맘에 들게 됐어
I was so in.
넌 전부터 내 맘속에 있었어
You're still in.
도나, 난 네 남자친구가 되고 싶어
Look, Donna,
I want to be your boyfriend.
난 네 생각 뿐이야
내 졸업반지 받아줄래?
And you're all I ever think about.
Will you wear my class ring?
- 좋아
- 좋아?
- Yes.
- Yes?
있잖아, 우리 나중에
키스하면 안 될까?
You know, why don't
we kiss on it later?
맞다. 토했지?
Right. The vomit.
아냐, 난 신경 안써
No, wait. You know what?
I don't care.
넌 내 여자친구야
You're my girlfriend.
야, 포먼
So, Forman, man...
오늘 밤 도나 일은 미안하다
I'm sorry about tonight with Donna.
그리고 네 저녁밥 슬쩍한 것도
And for taking your dinner.
우리 사이는 여전한 거지?
So, are we cool, man?
물론이지. 우린 친구잖아
Yeah, man. We've gotta be.
우린 유치원부터 친구였어
Look, we've been friends
since kindergarten.
여자 때문에 우리 사이가
어떻게 되진 않아
No girl's gonna come between us.
좋은 얘기야
That's great, man.
그러니까..
So...
도나가 너랑 헤어지고 나서
if Donna ever breaks up with you...
나랑 데이트하게 돼도
우린 계속 친구인 거지?
and starts dating me,
are we still friends?
아니
No.
오늘밤
Tonight,
난 그걸 하기 위해선 대가를
치러야 된다는 걸 배웠어
I learned there's
a price to be paid for doing it.
재키가 "영원히"란 말을 하더라고
She said, "forever," man.
진심인 거 같았어
And I think she meant it.
입안이 솜처럼 말라가
입안에 솜이 있는거 처럼 말야
The inside of my mouth feels like cotton.
As if cotton was in my mouth.
야, 켈소, 여자는
머핀같은 거야, 알아?
Kelso, man, women are
like muffins, okay?
일단 할번 맛을 보면 또 먹고 싶어서
별짓을 해도 참게 된단 말야
And once you've had a muffin, man...
you will put up with anything
to have another muffin.
그리고 여자들은 그걸 알아
이제 넌 걔한테 꽉 잡힌 거야
And they know that.
Now she really owns you, man.
하이드, 너 여자에 대해서
아는 게 정말 많은 거 같더라
Hyde, you sure know
a lot about women.
근데, 여태 여자를 제대로
사귀어 본 적은 없잖아
But, I mean, you've never really
had a steady girlfriend.
그건 어떻게 된 거야?
So, what's that all about?
어떻게 된 건지 말해 주지
내 정신세계는 너무 순수해서
I'll tell you what that's all about,
Forman. My mind is pure, man.
여자란 족속들에게
빠져들지 않는단 말야
I don't fall victim to the female race.
나 여기 있노라, 여자친구도 없이
네 놈들을 구원하기 위해
I'm here, sans girlfriend,
to help you guys out.
근데 나 질문이 있어, 하이드
Then I have a question, Hyde.
자위행위는 얼마나 하면
너무 많이 하는 거야?
How much masturbation is too much?
'너무 많이'라는 건
존재하지 않는단다, 페즈
No such thing as too much, Fez.
어땠냐?
How'd it go?
좋았어요
It was great.
- 엄마
- 찍었지롱
- Mom.
- Gotcha.
그 스포츠 재킷 멋있다고
한 사람 없었냐?
Anybody mention how nice
that sport coat was?
도나요
Donna.
거 봐라
그래, 재미있었냐?
There you go. So, you had fun?
네, 아빠. 고마워요
Yeah, Dad. Thanks.
네 신발에 당근 덩어리
붙어있는 거 아냐?
You know, you got a chunk of carrot
on your shoe there?
네, 아빠. 고마워요
Yeah, Dad. Thanks.
번역수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24